[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What title did director Martin Scorsese originally intend to give to his 1990 movie Goodfellas?", "correct_answer": "Wise Guy", "incorrect_answers": ["Naughty Boy", "Bad or Dead", "Baddest"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are rectangular pasta sheets rolled with a savory stuffing and then covered with a sauce.", "correct_answer": "cannelloni", "incorrect_answers": ["manicotti", "pantalone", "pipe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a type of beetle?", "correct_answer": "Burrowing beetle", "incorrect_answers": ["Long-horn beetle", "Stag beetle", "Flea beetle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the length of the worlds longest documented hair.", "correct_answer": "18.37 feet  (5.6 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["13.77 feet (4.2 m)", "23.95 feet (7.3 m)", "6.56 feet (2.0 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Daniel Radcliffe was offered the lead role in Eragon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress was nominated for a SAG Award for her part in the 2006 drama Babel?", "correct_answer": "Adriana Barraza", "incorrect_answers": ["Claire Danes", "Dakota Fanning", "Koji Yakamura"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does long in the tooth mean?", "correct_answer": "Old", "incorrect_answers": ["Tedious", "Wise", "Boring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won 5 Razzies in 2000?", "correct_answer": "Wild Wild West", "incorrect_answers": ["Message in a Bottle", "Get Carter", "8 Mile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fish may be consumed according to Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "Fish with fins and scales", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Shellfish", "Marine fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the special prize that will be given to one of the golden ticket holders in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "They will inherit the factory.", "incorrect_answers": ["A chocolate statue", "Eternal life", "A life supply of chocolate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of seafood is used for the making of the traditional Indonesian dish called Pempek?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Shrimp", "Oysters", "Octopus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term means fear of women?", "correct_answer": "Gynophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Dendrophobia", "Bibliophobia", "Anthrophobia"]}]